Guide to the the Richard W. Lyman, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0215
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Series 1
  - Dig-In Project, [1970] (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Dinkelspiel Auditorium, [1957-69] (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Dissertations / Challenges (contains only the file on Sparks, Marshall.), [1965-70] (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Distaff Club, [1969] (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Diplomas, 1965-70 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Dornbusch, Sanford, [1969-71] (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Double jeopardy, [1965] (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Doyle, Nr. Morris M. (Trustee), [1962-71] (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Drugs (Laws Regarding the use of Marijuana), 1965-68 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Drugs (LSD in Particu1ar), [1967-69] (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Druidism, [1971] (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - DuBridge, Advisor to Pres. Nixon on Science and Technology. See also: Pres. Science Adv. Comm. (Gen.), [1969-70] (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Duke University, [1968-69] (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - E General, [1967-71] (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - East-Asian Seminars, [1968] (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - East Palo Alto Day School, [1968-69] (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Editorial Projects For Education. The "EPE" 15-Minute Reports, [1967-70] (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Educational Career Service, [1968] (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Educational Innovations, [1969] (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Educational Resources Information Center, [1967] (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Educational Television, [1968-71] (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Satellite Communications Educational Television. [1970-71] (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Education As Awareness, [1971] (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Education Testing Service, [1967-70] (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Stanford Elementary School, [1966-70] (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Ely, Northcutt, [1966-67] (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Emergency Interim Legislation, [1968-70] (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Emeriti (General). See also: Policy Emeriti Retirement, [1962-68] (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - American Association On Emeriti, [1965-66] (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Supplementary Pension Program, [1962-68] (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Employment Agencies, [1968] (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Encina Fund, [1969] (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Encounter Groups. See also: Esalen Institute, [1969] (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Endowment Data, Stanford and Others, [1966] (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Enrollment Data, Stanford, [1957-70] (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Environmental Health Task Force Bay Area Comprehensive Health Planning Council, [1970] (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Environmental Law Society. See also: Coyote Hall (Activism), [1969] (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Environmental Matters. See also: Urban America, Inc, [1969-70] (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, [1968-69] (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Esalen Program/Institute. See also: Experiential Education, [1966-68] (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Brant Case, Esalen Institute, [1969] (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Escondido Village, [1959-60] (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - -Re: Rent Increase, [1969] (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Evers, Williamson M. (Bill), [1968] (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Examinations, [1969] (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Exchange Programs, [1963-70] (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Experiential Education. See also: Esalen Program, [1969] (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - F General, [1966-70] (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Faculty Club, [1965-69] (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Faculty Club Liquor License, [1969-70] (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - President's Dining Room, [1966-69] (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Faculty-Miscellaneous, [1966-67] (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Faculty Political Action Group, [1971] (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Faculty / Staff Directory, [1970] (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Fair Employment Practices Act - California Fair Labor Standards Act. See also: Equal Opportunities and Policy: Hiring Practices, [1967-69] (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Fall Out Shelters, [1968] (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Federal Aid to Education, [1968-69] (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, [1956-67] (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Pres. Nixon's Plan to Investigate Campus Violence (file empty) (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Federal Communications Commission, [1968] (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Federal Government - Stanford Relationship Research/Grants/Contracts, [1961-69] (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Fellowship of Christian Athletes, [1970] (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Film Festivals/Films, [1967-69] (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Film Making on Campus, [1969] (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Financial Reports, [1968-69] (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Financing (Stanford in Particular), [1969] (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Financing Higher Education. See also: California Constitutional Reform, [1969-70] (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Financing Private institutions. See also: Cornell University For Study of Government Education Relations or California Constitution Revision Commission, [1968-70] (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Biddle Bill (ACA 47), [1970] (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - Financing Public Education in California, [1968] (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Peter Coutts-Frenchman's Terrace (Low / Moderate Income Housing), AD 13.2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Fires/Other Than Stanford, [1968] (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Flag of the United States, Etiquette, [1955-71] (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Flags, [1967] (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Flowers (Ordering of), [1965] (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Fluoridation of Water Supply, [1969-70]; AD 13.9.2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Scholars/Students, [l968-70] (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Forensics, [1966-70]; St3.15 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Form Letters, [1968-70]; AD3.9 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Formal Processions, [1965]; AD11.7.5 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Forum 70, [1970] (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Founding Grant, [1969-70]; AD7.6 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Fraternities Restrictive Clause, [1957-65]; AD 8.18.8 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Fraternities General, [1953-70] (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Alpha Phi Omega, 1964-70; AD8.18.8 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Fraternity Beta Chi, [1966-70] (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Delta Chi, [1967] (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon Fraternity (Housing), [1964-68] (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Delta Tau Delta, [1966-70] (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity. See: Demonstration Housing (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Disaffiliates With The National Fraternity. Zeta Alpha Pi (New Name), [1965-70] (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Fraudulence/Possible Fraud, [1967]; AD 7.7 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Frost Amphitheater, [1963-70] (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Fundamental Standard, [1963-68] (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - G General, [1965-69] (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Gifted Children, [1965-69] (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Glee Club, [1968-70]; St 3.16 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Golf: Golf Course Use, [1965-70]; AD 12.14.7/23 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Governance of the University. See also: Gardner Comm. to Study Structure of the Board of Trustees, 1969, [1968-69]; AD 7.8 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Grades/Grading, [1970]; AA3.l3 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - -Pass/Fail Grading System, [1966-71] (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Graduate Reception. (Graduate Division Handles), [1969]; AD 11.7.8 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Graduation Requirements. See: Course-Credit Issues (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Grass Roots, (Environment), 1970; AD.13.9 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Grievance Procedure see: Policy (Cases filed: Personnel and Employee Relations Dept.) (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - The Grove Project. See: Demonstration Housing (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - John Grube, [1969] (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - University of Guanabara in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil. See: Exchange Programs (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Gubser, Charles S. - U.S. Rep, 1965-70 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Guest Rooms. See: Room Reservations (Guest Rooms) (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Gunther, Professor Gerald, [1969] (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Fund Raising, [1969-70] (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Major Fund Raising Campaign. (file empty) See: Cabinet / Committee on Gift Program-Trustees, (1971-72) (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - H, [1966-70] (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Hammond, Eddie, [1966] (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Mary Hanson, [1967-70] (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - David Harris/Joan Baez, [1967-72] (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Hart, George D. [1970] See also: Index Card For More (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Harvard University, [1969-70] (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Harvard Recognition System (25 Year Employees), [1971]; U 8.23 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Hashing, [1968]; St 3.13.1 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Hayakawa, Dr. SI, [1969-71] (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Head Start Program, [1966-67] (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Heffner, Hubert, [1969-70] (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - William R. Hewlett, [1963-70] (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - High School Day, AD11.7.9. (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Higher education, Case For / Against (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965. See also: Financial Aids, [1966-68] (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Higher Education Act of 1963. Facilities. See also: Coordinating Council for Higher Education, [1964-71] (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Hitch, Charles J, [1969] (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Hoax, [1965-69] (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Home Exchanges, [1966] (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Homosexuality/Homophile League, [1967-68] (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Honor Code, The Stanford, 1955-59 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Honor Societies, 1968-70 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Hoover, Allan, 1966-70 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Hoover, Herbert Jr, 1955-68 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Lou Henry Hoover House. See: President's House (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Herbert Hoover Pavilion, 1959-69 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Housing, Emeriti/Senior Staff, 1965-68 (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Housing-Low Cost/Low Income. Graduate Student Housing, [1969-70] (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Arguments Re: Use of Land for Low-Income Housing, [1970] (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Relates to Housing For Graduate Students, [1970-71] (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Alan S. Maremont To Advise on the Feasibility of Rental Housing on Stanford Lands, [1969] (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Minority Housing, [1970]; AD 8.18.11 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Housing - Raven Proposal Regarding Old Corporation Yard, [1968] (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Housing-General Policy, 1965-69 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Co-educational Housing, [1967-70] (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Visiting Hours, Coeducational Housing, [1968] (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Housing Coordinator (Student), [1969] (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Housing (Student): Includes Demonstration Housing, [1967-70] (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Alternative Homes. (empty file) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Florence Moore Hall, [1967-69] (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Wilbur Hall, [1967] (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - The Grove Project, [1966-68] (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Serra-Donner Controversy, [1967-68] (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Stern Jacks Housing, [1966-70] (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Housing: Married Student, [1964-69] (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Housing (Men). [1963-69] (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Housing Research Group, [1969] (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Fraternity Cluster III, [1967-68] (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Housing Available in England, [1969] (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Howard University, [1968] (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Hubert Humphrey, [1966-67] (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Hutchinson, Eric, [1967-68] (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Hypnosis Workshop, [1970] (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - I, [1969-71] (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Immigration, [1966-69] (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Index of Social Responsibility for American Business, [1969] (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Industrial Park, [1968-70]; AD 13.8 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Information Bulletin, [1967-70] (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - In Loco Parentis, [1967] (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Inner Quad, [1970] (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Institute for Educational Management. See: Sloan Program-Business School Dept (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Institute in Germany for Advanced Study, [1968] (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Institute of International Education, [1965-69] (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Institute for Public Policy Analysis, [1968-71] (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Institute for the Study of Human Problems, [1966-69] (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Institute of Human Relations, [1971]; O3.40 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Institute for the Study of Non-Violence, [1968-70]; O3.39 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Insurance (General)/Property, [1969-70]; AD 12.8.1 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Insurance ASSU, [1969]; AD 12.8. 1/2 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Insurance Claim Agent, [1970] (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Earthquakes/Studies of, Insurance, Etc, [1969-70] (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Insurance. (Fire), [1968-69] (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Insurance-Group Life Plans (Faculty and Non-Faculty), [1955-67] (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Insurance (Student Hospitalization), [1970] (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Insurance Cases and possible cases, [1965-66] (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Long Term Disability Income Plan, [1966] (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - United Medical Clinics Plan Insurance, Medical Service Plan-Insurance, [1965-71] (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Re: Modification of Health Plan, [1966-70] (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Insurance: T.I.A.A, [1960-70] (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Insurance: Group and Individual Travel Accident, [1957-60] (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Insurance: Unemployment, [1965-70] (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Insurance Pool, Voluntary Property, [1970] (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Insurance (Vehicles), [1968] (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Intelligence Quotient, [1969] (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, [1967-68] (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Interdepartmental Assembly, [1970] (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Interdepartmental Majors, [1967-69] (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Intern Programs, [1962-70] (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - J.E. Wallace Sterling Internship (Formerly Stanford In Sacramento Intern Program), [1966-69] (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - International African Institute, [1964-70] (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - International Association (Institute of International Relations and the International Club Merged to form International Association), [1965-71] (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - International Association of University Presidents, [1967-68] (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - IAU 5th General Conference 8/29/70 - 9/5/70, Montreal, [1965-70] (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - International Club, [1963-66] (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - International Congress of Classical Studies, [1969] (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - International Education Act of 1966, [1966-69] (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - International Research and Exchanges Board-U.S. Dept. of State, [1969-70]; G 3.16.6 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - International Student Affairs. (changed from Foreign Student Advisor-1965), [1968] (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - International Study Project, Inc (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - International University of Europe, [1969] (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - International Voluntary Services, [1966-68] (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Inter-Tribal Council of California, [1968] (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Invitations, [1970] (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Invitations to Speak (Regretted), [1970] (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Invitations (Lyman Host), [1969] (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Invitations (Special) Hold for Reference, [1965,1968] (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Invitations/To Speak, Other. (Glover and Others). (file empty) (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Involvement Corps (Pilot Project to Bring About "Constructive Revolution"), [1968] (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - J, 1966-67 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Jack and Jill Conference, [1968] (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Jamaica Vacation Applicants, [1961-65] (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Japan and Japanese Affairs, 1966-67 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Jasper Ridge Biological Experimental Area, 1966-67 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Jones, Thomas V. Trustee. (file empty) (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Journal of Higher Education, [1968] (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Judicial Procedures. (RE: Legislative and Judicial Charter.), [1968-70] (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Judicial Procedures (Probation and Suspension/Definitions of: Prosecutor/Attorney General), [1969-70] (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Junior Faculty Forum, [1969] (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Junior Science and Humanities Symposium, 1964-65 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Jury Duty/Commissioner, Santa Clara County.(file missing - no out card), 1962-69 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - K General, [1965-70] (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Keio University (Student Exchange Program). See: Exchange Program (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Kemnitzer, Wm. J, [1962-67] (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Kent State University in Ohio, [1970] (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Clark Kerr, [1964-67] (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Kingscote Apartments, [1963-69] (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Kline, Stephen J, [1968-69] (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - KQED (Includes auction), [1970] (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Krebiozen, [1965-66] (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Thomas H. Kuchel, U.S. Senator, [1965-68] (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - KZSU, [1966-70] (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - L General, [1965-70] (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Lacrosse, [1964-70] (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Lake Lagunita, [1962-69] (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Ladera Dam, [1962-69] (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Land, Edwin H, [1964-68] (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Landscaping, [1970] (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Languages (Gen. Misc.), 1965-69 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Leadership Development Program, [1969] (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Lee, Dr. Russell V, 1968-71 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Legal Aid Society, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Liberation Week Activities, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Librarian Association, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Liquor Policy, 1968-70 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Liquor - Legal Opinions, licenses (Policy) Legality on Campus and 1/2 mile zone, 1955-70 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Serving of Alcohol in University Buildings (Other than Residence Halls - Must be Ok'd by President's Office.), 1966-70 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Long Range Estimates/Planning, 1967-70 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Long Range Estimates/Planning, 1967-70 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Lowenstein, Allard, 1963-70 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - M, [1963-70] (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Mack Burnell, [1970] (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - The Mafia, [1969] (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Maggie's Farm, [1969] (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Mail, Interdepartmental, Etc, [1967-70] (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Re: Bulk Mailing, [1969-70] (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Manganiello, Aaron J, [1968] (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Mailings. (Art, Music, Summer Festival, Calendars), [1967-69] (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Bayless Manning, Dean of the Law School, [1968] (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Management Consultants. (See: Cresap, Etc.) (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Manzanita Park (Trailers), [1969-70] (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Roscoe Maples Pavilion, [1958-69] (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Problem of Acoustics, [1969] (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence With Mrs. Maples, [1969-70] (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Marine Corps, [1968-69] (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, [1969] (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - May 2nd Movement (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Mayfield House (Cooperative Residence), [1968-69] (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - McClellan Committee. - Senate Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations of the Committee on Government Operations, [1969] (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Letters of Response to our Handling of the Subpoena, [1969] (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - McCloskey, Paul N. Jr. (The Hon.), [1968-70] (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - John A. McCone, [1969] (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - R. C. McCurdy, [1961-68] (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - McGovern, George (Senator of South Dakota), [1969] (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Medical Coverage, Students, [1968] (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Basic Medical Plan for Faculty and Staff (Increased Staff Benefit Rate), 1969 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Medical Student Association, [1969] (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Memberships, Stanford. Lists and Miscellaneous Information, [1962-69] (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Memorial Auditorium, [1965-69] (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Memorials (War), [1965-68] (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Mendicants, [1965-67] (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Stanford-Menlo Park Relations Including H.U.D. Model City Program. See also U.S. Dept. H.U.D, [1967-68] (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Menlo School and College, [1969] (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Mexican-American Affairs, [1966-69] (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Mexican/American Affairs, Assistant to the President for. (John Johnson's search committee files (2), (1969-70) (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Mexican-American Seminars, [1969-70] (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Mexican-American Seminars, Search for the Director of. (John Johnson's file, 1970) (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Mid-Peninsula Christian Ministry, [1968] (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Mid-Peninsula Free University, [1968-70] (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Mid-Peninsula Health Facilities Planning Council, [1966-68] (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Miller, Robert, [1968] (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Mills College, [1966-69] (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Minority Education/Programs, [1969-70] (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Affirmative Action-Program Minority Employment, [1969-70] (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Minority Programs (funding for), [1969] (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Minority Groups and Acton Taken, [1967-70] (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Minority Demands, Minority Groups and Action Taken, [1969-71] (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Minority Students, [1972] (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Monterey Institute of Foreign Studies, [1968] (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Moran, Hugh A, 1966-69 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Mothers' Club of Stanford University, 1969-70 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Motto, The Stanford, 1966-68 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Movimiento Estudiantil Chicano de Aztlan. See: Chicanos File (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Multi-National Universities, 1967-68 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - N General, 1966-67 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Nairobi College, 1969-70 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Names for Stanford Streets and Parks, 1957-69 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Names for Resident Units and Office Buildings, 1954-69 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1963-70 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - National Advisory Council on Education Professions Development, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1966-70 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Conference at NASA ib 6-23-69 re: The Relationships Between Universities and Government Agencies, [1969] (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs, 1962-69 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1957-68 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1968-70 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - National Center for Primate Biology. California Advisory Committee (Proposal), [1967] (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1966-70 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Freshman Participation in All Varsity Sports Except Basketball and Football, [1967-68] (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Re: Financial Aid to Athletes (See also file re: Financial Aid to Athletes--P.E. Dept.) [1970] (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - National Commission on the Causes and Prevention of Violence. See: Violence File (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - National. Commission on. Libraries, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - National Defense Educational Act. See also: Fellowships, 1962-70 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - National Defense Student Loan Funds, 1958-70 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - National Education Association. American Association for Higher Education, 1965-69 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - National Industrial Conference Board, 1960-69 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - National Institute of Public Affairs. See: Fellowships (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - National Labor Relations Board (Unions), 1964-69 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - National Medal of Science, 1966-69 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - W.K.H. Panofsky, National Medal of Science (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - National Plan for Emergency Preparedness -Filed (Office of Emergency Planning) (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - National Service. See: Community for Relevant Education (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - National Student Association (NSA), 1962-69 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Natural Disaster Study, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Naval Research Advisory Committee, 1966-68 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Nazis Activities, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Nelson, Lyle M, 1960-71 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - New York Office(Stanford), 1964-69 (Box 26, Folder 41)